emagister.co.uk 2012-10-04

# Emagister

**Privacy Policy**

Effective on February 9, 2010 

This privacy statement describes how Emagister UK collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.emagister.co.uk. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

Emagister UK is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.emagister.co.uk. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Webmaster at info@emagister.co.uk. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at [http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=)

**TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.**

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We collect the following personal information from you when you register to use our site 

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, and phone number 

If you wish to register your training company or educational institution we will ask for your trading name, address, a contact person, email address and telephone number. We ask for this information so that we may contact you with regard to adding your centre to our existing list of registered providers, and so that potential students and course candidates can get more information about you as a training entity and the courses you offer. 

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. 

We use this information to 

  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Respond to your questions and concerns

If you wish to learn more about certain courses or course providers, we will pre-fill the forms with your name and email address. 

Once you have signed up for the service you have the option to show your user profile along with the courses you have attended. Please be aware that if you make your profile visible, other users of the site may view your information. 

**Communications From the Site**

When you register with www.emagister.co.uk we will send you a confirmation email with your login details. This email is not promotional in nature and you may not opt-out of receiving this transactional email. We do not send promotional emails at this time. 

We do not share your personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional use. 

**Tell-A-Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about courses that they may be interested, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Emagister UK stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral process. 

Your friend may contact us at [info@emagister.co.uk](mailto:info@emagister.co.uk) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

**Information provided by minors**

Minors under 16 cannot register to use emagister.net without prior consent from their parents or guardians. If you are under 16 and have entered the site without notifying your parents you cannot register as a user. 

**Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as sending out email communications on our behalf or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us. 

We may also disclose your personal information 

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Emagister UK is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

We share your personal information with other companies so that they can market their products or services to you. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at [info@emagister.co.uk](mailto:info@emagister.co.uk). 

**Security**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [info@emagister.co.uk](mailto:info@emagister.co.uk)

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information. 

_Web beacons_

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons that are employed by third party service providers (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used. 

_Links to Other Web Sites_

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Emagister UK. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

**Additional Policy Information**

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review or update your personal information to ensure it is accurate you may login to "My Emagister" and go to "My Account", or contact us at [info@emagister.co.uk](mailto:info@emagister.co.uk). You also have the option of cancelling your account within "My Emagister". 

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

**Contact Information**

You can contact us by writing or email us at the address below: 

Emagister Servicios de Formación, S.L.  
81 Oxford Street  
London  
W1D 2EU  
United Kingdom  
Email: [info@emagister.co.uk](mailto:info@emagister.co.uk)
